Shriniwas Dargad

+919405723349 | shriniwasd110@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/shriniwas-dargad-443471193/

OBJECTIVE

I am a passionate Electronics and Communication Engineering graduate with a GPA of 8.5. During my college years, I gained practical experience through internships in Human Resource Management and Digital Marketing. I also worked as a Mathematics Faculty at Byju's Tuition Center, where I honed my teaching skills.

In addition to my academic achievements, I have successfully completed projects such as "Digital Art Drawing in the Air Through Gesture" and "GSM Based Automatic Irrigation System." These projects showcase my ability to innovate and contribute to the field of Human-Computer Interaction and agricultural development.

I possess a strong skill set in front-end development, including HTML, CSS, jQuery, and JavaScript. Furthermore, I have expertise in SEO Copywriting, Digital Marketing strategies, Python programming, and various online marketing techniques such as Google Analytics and Ads.

With my diverse background and passion for technology-driven solutions, I am ready to make a positive impact in any organization that values innovation and growth.

EDUCATION

TSSM'S BHIVARABAI SAWANT COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING AND RESEARCH Bachelor's degree PUNE 2018 - 2022

Electronics and Communication Engineering

Shri Mahant Ramgiri Baba Jr. College., Watur XII

High school or equivalent 2017 – 2018

WORK EXPERIENCE

Mathematics Faculty

Aug 2022 - Jun 2023

Byju's Tuition Center - Nanded

- 1. Teaching Mathematics to students online as well as offline.
- 2. Teaching CBSE, ICSE and State board syllabus.
- 3. Designing and managing Curriculum
- 4. Preparing and conducting exam papers

Digital Marketing and Research and Development

Apr 2021 – Feb 2022

Spade EMS

GoDutch - Pune

Internship

Full-time

Spade Phagwara - Work from home

- 1. Learnt about event management and event marketing
- 2. Learnt to find guests for the events
- 3. Learnt how to choose topics for event and how to market those topics

Program Manager (BDA)

Feb 2021 – Apr 2022

1. Learnt all the marketing strategies and product management

Internship

- 2. Coordinated with the team of 8 members as a team lead
- 3. Got an idea of on field marketing and convincing people about the product
- 4. Built team of 8 interns from college and executed marketing as well as sales campaigns.

Human Resources Intern

Human Resource Management

Internship

Jan 2020 - Feb 2021

Anar - work from home

- 1. Learnt to shortlist candidate by their applications.
- 2. Learnt to interview candidates
- 3. Learnt to build a team from scratch and managing the work of the team and maintaining work relevant atmosphere in team

PROJECTS

Digital Art Drawing in the Air Through Gesture

This project is about Digital Art in which we can make virtual drawing in the air with the use of our finger tips. It helps in the development of Human-computer interaction (HCI)

GSM Based Automatic Irrigation System

This project is about the automatic irrigation system using GSM which helps in the agricultural development. As automation is taking place in numerous industries, why not in agricultural fields. So, we have made this project to help various farmers using GSM and make their lives easier than before. This project also helps in conservation of water as there is no wastage of water.

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, jQuery, JavaScript, C, SEO Copywriting, Digital Marketing, Python,

Search Engine Optimization (SEO), Web Development, Google Analytics, Content Marketing, Google Ads,

Search Engine Marketing (SEM), Online Marketing, Pay Per Click, Influencer Marketing, Keyword Research,

Digital Marketing Certification, YouTube Advertising, Sales, Mathematics, Social Skills, Marketing